안녕, 드라마 다이제스트에 나온
글자 맞추기를 하고 있었는데 말야
Hi. So I'm doing the Soap Opera Digest
crossword puzzle..
세로 문제에 누가 나왔는지 알아?
and guess who is the clue
for three down?
"우리 인생의 나날들에 출연한
빈칸 트리비아니"
"Days of Our Lives star,
blank Tribbiani."
나잖아! 내가 빈칸이야!
That's me! I'm blank!
멋있다! 빈칸이 우리 친구라니
난 만지기까지 하고 있어
How cool! We know three down.
I'm touching three down.
맞았어, 자기
Yeah, you are, baby.
내가 유부녀인 거 알면서
빈칸이 왜 이러지?
Three down knows I'm married.
What's three down doing?
이제 널 인터뷰하러 찾아오겠지?
Do they call to tell you you're in it?
아냐, 이미 제의가 들어왔었는데
내가 안한다고 했어
No. They wanted to do
a profile on me. I said no.
왜 거절했어?
Why'd you say no?
저번에 인터뷰한거
기억 안 나?
Remember the last interview I did?
내가 대사 쓴다고 했다가
작가가 엄청 화가 나
I said I write my own lines,
the writers got mad..
내 배역을 단번에 죽여 버렸잖아
내가 뭔 말을 내뱉을지 누가 알아?
and I fell down an elevator shaft.
Who knows what I'd say now?
머리 속에 뇌가 있다면
참 좋을텐데 말야
If only there was something
in your head to control what you say.
그래도 이번 인터뷰는
꼭 해야 돼
Come on, you'll keep it
in check this time.
대중의 관심을 끌면 네 경력에도
도움이 된다고, 넌 자격이 있어
The publicity would be good for you.
You deserve that.
인터뷰할 때 이걸 꼭 집어넣어
"내 친구 레이첼 그린"
In the interview, you could mention,
I don't know, "gal pal Rachel Green."
"한심이 레이첼 그린"이 아니고?
Is that "gal pal" spelled L-O-S-E-R?
- 쟤 말 듣지 마, 부탁이야
- 알았어, 할게
-Okay, don't listen to him. Please?
-Fine, all right, I'll do it.
그 대신 내가 경거망동 못하게
다들 인터뷰할 때 와서 봐줘야 돼
You have to be there to stop me
if I say something stupid.
잠시만? 아니면 끝날 때까지?
우리도 직업이 있거든
Just then, or all the time?
Because we have jobs, you know?
끝까지 있을테니 이것만 명심해
We'll be there the whole time.
Just remember:
내 친구 레이첼 그린
Gal pal, Rachel Green.
나 드라마 다이제스트에 나와!
시시한 글자 맞추기가 아니라
I'm gonna be in Soap Opera Digest!
And not just in the dumb crossword.
네가 자랑스러워
Seriously, proud of you.
프렌즈 시즌 8
'조이의 인터뷰'
- 시간 내주셔서 감사합니다
- 별말씀을, 제가 영광이죠
-Thanks for taking the time for this.
-Not at all. Happy to do it.
우리 너무 티 날까?
You think we're being obvious?
전혀, 목이 뻣뻣한 것뿐인데 뭐
입도 좀 비틀어지고
No. We're just four people with
neck problems, who talk like this.
이리로 오라고 해서 놀랐어요
It's great that we met here.
잡지사에서 돈 낸다 하면
다들 비싼 식당으로 가거든요
When people hear the magazine's paying,
they want a big, fancy restaurant.
잡지사가 돈 내는 줄 몰랐어요
Actually, I didn't know
the magazine was paying.
상관없어요, 공짜 음식이 아닌
팬들을 위해 하는 거니까
Wouldn't have mattered. I do this
for the fans, not the free food.
- 주문하시겠습니까?
- 커피요
-Can I get you anything?
-Coffee.
머핀 몽땅 다 갖다 줘
And I'll have all the muffins.
- 안녕
- 우린 말하면 안돼
-Hey.
-We're not talking.
이제야 살겠군
Oh, finally.
프로필을 읽어봤는데
여러 작품에 출연하셨더군요
According to your bio,
you've done quite a bit of work.
어떤 역할이 가장 기억에 남죠?
Anything that you're
particularly proud of?
당신이 원하는 건 내 몸뚱아리
All you want is a dingle
당신이 탐내는 건 격렬한 몸짓
What you envy's a shwang
딸랑딸랑 방울을 높이 울려라
A thing through which you can tinkle
그냥 늘어지게 해도 상관없어
Or play with, or simply let hang
이런 일 자주 있으시죠?
우유를 마시고 싶은데
This ever happen?
You want a glass of milk..
그 놈의 구멍이 열려야 말이죠!
but these darn cartons
are so hard to open!
맞아, 마이크
Boy, you said it, Mike.
- 뭔가 방법이 있을 거야!
- 맞아, 케빈!
-There 's gotta be a better way!
- There is, Kevin!
케빈은 이걸 처음 써보는데
아주 쉬워요, 해봐
This is the first time
he's ever used this. It's easy.
- 어떤 우유든 다 되죠
- 쉽네
-This works in any milk carton.
-It is easy.
이젠 우유를 매일 마실 수 있어
Now I can have milk every day.
이제 끝인가요, 빅터?
So this is it, Victor?
그래, 그런 것 같군, 난 이제
Yeah, I guess it is. And so..
우주선에 탑승할 거야
I'm gonna get on this spaceship..
그리곤 대체 연료를 찾아
블라곤 7에 가는 거지
and I'm gonna go to Blargon 7
in search of alternative fuels.
200년이 흘러 돌아오면
당신은 오래 전에 꽥 했겠지
But when I return 200 years from now,
you'll be long gone.
하지만 난 그대로일 걸
But I won't have aged at all.
그러니 당신 고손녀한테
날 찾으라고 전해줘
So you tell your great-great-
granddaughter to look me up.
왜냐하면
Because, Adrian..
내 사랑
baby..
걔랑 데이트하고 싶거든
I'm gonna want to meet her.
나 나왔어
복사기 고치러 온 거야
Here I come.
I'm coming to fix the copier.
그런데 접근은 못하고
생각하지, '어떻게 하지?'
I can't get to the copier.
I'm thinking, "What do I do?"
둘이 섹스하는 걸 지켜봐
그러다, 들어봐, 내 대사야
So I just watch them have sex.
And then I say.. Wait, here's my line:
용지 트레이가 불쌍해
You know, that's bad
for the paper tray.
- 멋있어, 친구
- 잠깐, 또 나와
-Nice work, my friend.
-Wait, you see me again.
남자 엉덩이에 가렸어
Hang on, the guy's butt's blocking me.
저거 나야, 저거 나야,
저거 나야
There I am. There I am. There I am.
너무 많아서
하나만 고르기가 힘드네요
There are so many things,
it's hard to pick just one.
커피 마셔야겠어, 뭐 갖다줄까?
I'm getting coffee. Want anything?
- 블루베리 머핀이랑 국화차
- 더블 라테
-A blueberry muffin and chamomile tea.
-Double latte.
- 베이글에..
- 예의상 물어본 거야
-A bagel with only..
-I was just being polite.
일 안할땐 어떠세요?
여가 시간엔 뭘 하시죠?
How about when you're not working?
What do you do in your spare time?
저 광대 좀 봐, 자기가
이 강 주인이라도 되나 봐
Look at this clown. He thinks
he can take up the whole river.
꺼져, 이 얼간아!
Get out of the way, jackass!
배 이름이 연안 경비대가 뭐야?
Who names their boat
Coast Guard, anyway?
진짜 연안 경비대야
That is the Coast Guard.
연안 경비대가 왜 여깄어?
연안은 저쪽이잖아!
What are they doing out here?
The coast is way over there!
이건 기적이야
This is unbelievable.
조이가 숨 안 쉬고
4분째 버티고 있다고
Joey has been holding his breath
for almost four minutes.
날 죽이려는 거야?
Dude, are you trying to kill me?
아주 생산적인 하루를 보냈나 봐
Well, I see you've had
a very productive day.
- 카우보이 모잔 그렇지 않아?
- 이리 와, 재밌어!
-Isn't the cowboy hat a little much?
-Come on, it's fun!
알았어
All right.
이거 여자 모자 아냐?
Isn't this a woman's hat?
주둥이 닥치고 가서 차나 끓여
Dude, stop talking crazy
and make us some tea.
저 포르노 채널 끄는게 좋겠어
We have to turn off the porn.
네 말이 맞아
I think you're right.
- 준비됐어?
- 하나
-All right, ready?
-One.
- 둘, 셋
- 셋
-Two, three.
-Three.
기분 좋다
That's kind of nice.
- 속이 후련해
- 그래
-It's kind of a relief.
-Yeah.
- 아직도 나오나 확인해볼까?
- 그래
-You wanna see if we still have it?
-Yeah.
공짜 포르노야!
공짜 채널이라고!
Free porn! We have free porn here!
여가 시간엔
눈이 빠질 때까지 책을 읽죠
In my spare time, I read to the blind.
심봉사 활동도 하고요
And I'm also a mento for kids.
- 심봉사요?
- 심봉사요, 아시잖아요
-A mento?
-You know, a mento. A role model.
- 심봉사요?
- 네
-A mento?
-Right.
- 혹시 봉사 말씀이세요?
- 나 봉사 아녜요
-Like the candy?
-As a matter of fact, I do.
독자들은 배우들이
어떻게 다 날씬한지 궁금해하죠
Our readers always want to know how
soap stars stay in such great shape.
비결이라도 있으세요?
Do you have a fitness regime?
그냥 제대로 챙겨 먹고
운동을 많이 합니다
We stars usually just try to eat right
and get lots of exercise.
1시간 동안 공을 한번도
안 떨어뜨린 거 알아?
You know we've thrown this
without dropping it for an hour?
정말이야?
Are you serious?
30분 전에 알았는데
징크스 생길까봐 말 안했어
I realized it a half-hour ago,
but I didn't want to jinx it.
- 우리 진짜 잘하네
- 그래
-Wow, we are pretty good at this.
-Yeah.
이런, 점심을 깜박했어
Hey, we totally forgot about lunch.
밥 먹는거 까먹긴 난생 처음이야
That's the first time
I've ever missed a meal.
허리띠가 좀 느슨하네
My pants are a little loose.
왜 그래?
What's wrong with you?
아령을 드는데 갑자기
배가 찢어질듯 아프잖아
I got this blinding pain in my stomach
when I was lifting weights.
그래서 기절했지 뭐
And then I passed out.
일어서질 못하겠어
심각한 건 아니니 걱정 마
I haven't been able to stand up since.
But I don't think it's serious.
탈장 같은데, 어서 병원에 가봐
Sounds like a hernia.
Go to the doctor.
싫어!
No way!
배에 볼록 튀어나온거 때문이라면
몰라도 탈장 때문엔 안가!
If I go to the doctor, it's for this
thing sticking out of my stomach!
내가 왜 또 운동을 시작했지?
Why'd I have to start
working out again?
7kg, 너 때문이야!
Damn you, fifteens!
- 그게 뭐야?
- 트라이플, 층이 여러 개야
-What is it?
-A trifle. It has layers.
맨먼저 카스텔라, 그 다음엔 잼
A layer of ladyfingers,
then a layer of jam.
다음엔 커스터드
내가 요리책 없이 만들었어
Then custard,
which I made from scratch.
래스베리, 다시 카스텔라
콩과 양파를 넣어 볶은 쇠고기
Raspberries, more ladyfingers,
beef sauteed with peas and onions.
그리고 다시 커스터드
Then a little bit more custard.
발냄새가 나
It tastes like feet.
좋은데 뭐
I like it.
- 농담해?
- 왜? 커스터드, 좋잖아
-Are you kidding?
-What's not to like? Custard, good.
잼, 좋잖아! 고기, 따봉!
Jam, good. Meat, good!
상태가 말이 아냐, 조이
Well, you don't look good, Joe.
냉장고가 고장나서
할수 없이 다 먹었어
Well, the fridge broke,
so I had to eat everything.
샌드위치 햄, 아이스크림, 라임
Cold cuts, ice cream, limes.
참, 갈색 용기 안에 든 건 뭐야?
Hey, what was in that brown jar?
- 안에 남았어?
- 아니
-That's still in there?
-Not anymore.
이건 바닥에 안닿았어
This piece doesn't have floor on it.
- 선 넘어오지 마
- 그만좀 해
-Stick to your side.
-Hey, come on, now.
메뉴가 뭐야?
All right, what are we having?
전 다이어트는 안믿습니다
뭐든 적당한게 좋은 거죠
I don't believe in these crazy diets.
Just everything in moderation.
머핀 나왔어
Your muffins.
나갈때 싸줘
I'll take those to go.
심봉사 활동요
For the kids.
참, 이걸 물어봐야지
I know what I wanted to ask.
오래 전 드라마에서 맡은 역할이
죽은 적이 있는데, 어떻게 된 거죠?
They killed you off years ago.
What happened there?
너무 멍청했어요, 인터뷰에서
해선 안되는 말을 했죠
I said some stuff in an interview
I shouldn't have said.
- 오늘은 그런 일 없을 겁니다
- 그렇군요
-But that is not gonna happen today.
-Understood.
- 무슨 말을 했는데요?
- 뭐랬냐면..
-So, what'd you say back then?
-I said that I..
- 조이!
- 안녕?
-Hey, Joey!
-How you doing?
여긴 셸리야, 날 인터뷰하고 있어
셸리, 내 친구들이에요
This is Shelly. She's interviewing me.
Shelly, these are my friends.
전 조이 친구 레이첼 그린이에요
정보가 필요하면 저한테 오세요
Hi, I'm gal pal Rachel Green.
If you want the dirt, come to me.
얘가 조이 애일지 누가 알아요?
This might be Joey's baby, who knows?
농담이에요, 지금까지
레이첼 그린이었습니다
I'm just kidding.
Seriously, gal pal Rachel Green.
태중의 아기를 모욕한 임산부죠
Who just lost the respect
of her unborn child.
커피 좀 데워올게요
I'm gonna go get this warmed up.
- 조이, 잘하고 있어
- 바보 같은 말도 안 했고
-You're doing great.
-So far, nothing stupid.
- 심봉사?
- 나 심봉사 활동 안해
-Mento?
-No, thanks.
모두 조이의 친구라고 하셨는데
독자들에게 해줄 말씀 없으세요?
As Joey's friends, is there anything
our readers should know?
조이는 정말 아주 멋진 친구예요
No, just that he is a great guy.
잡지에 나가려고 별 짓을 다하네
That'll get you
into Soap Opera Digest.
조이는..
Well, I..
우리 친구 조이는
I'd like to say that Joey..
우리 인생의 나날들을
풍성하게 해준 장본인이죠
truly has enriched
the days of our lives.
조이는 이 세상에서 가장
뜨겁고도 달콤한 사람이에요
I think that you don't expect
someone so hot to be so sweet.
- 멋진데요, 이름이 뭐죠?
- 피비 부페이요
-I like that. What's your name?
-Phoebe Buffay.
- 철자가 어떻게 되죠?
- '피비'할 때 ㅍ, '피비'할 때 이
-How do you spell that?
-It's P as in Phoebe. H as in Heebie.
'피비'할 때 ㅂ
'피비'할 때 이
O as in Obie. E as in Ebie.
'부페이'할 때 부페
그리고 '부페이'할 때 이요
B as in Beebee.
And E as in, "ello there, mate!"
멋지네요, 만나서 반가웠어요
Great. It was nice meeting you.
- 우리도요
- 고마워요
-Yeah, you too.
-Thanks.
친구가 참 많으신 것 같은데
단짝 친구는 누구죠?
It seems you have a lot of friends.
Who is your best friend?
왜 2개야?
How come you have two?
이건 네 거야
Well, this one's for you.
- 정신차려!
- 그게 안돼
-Get out!
-No, I can't.
너 무진장 감동한 거 알아
이건 그냥 팔찌가 아냐
I know how much this means to you.
This isn't just about jewelry.
우리가 단짝 친구라는 걸
알려주는 증표라고
It's about you and me
and the fact that we're best buds.
이런게 우정이지? 그런가봐!
Is this friendship? I think so!
내밀어 봐! 우린 팔찌 친구야!
Check it out! We're bracelet buddies!
다 그렇게 불러줄걸
That's what they'll call us!
- 미안해
- 괜찮아, 걱정마
-I'm sorry.
-It's all right. Don't worry about it.
괜찮긴, 얼룩이 남을 거라고
That's gonna leave a stain.
레이첼, 괜찮아
여긴 조이의 집이야
Rach, hey, it's fine.
You're at Joey's.
- 정말?
- 그럼, 잘 봐
-Really?
-Yeah, look.
- 이렇게 살긴 처음이야
- 알아!
-I've never lived like this before.
-I know!
음식 버리지마, 그럼 벌받아
Well, don't waste it.
I mean, it's still food. Jeez!
난 죄책감 느껴
좋은 친구가 되고 싶다고
I feel guilty.
I wanna be a good friend..
젠장, 난 좋은 친구야
그러니 닥치고 눈감아
and damn it, I am a good friend.
So shut up and close your eyes.
넌 좋은 친구야
You are a good friend.
오디션은 오늘 아침이었고
배역은 못 따냈어
The audition was this morning,
and I didn't get it.
어쨌든 키스 하난 죽인다
레이첼은 진짜 봉 잡은 거야
But that was a hell of a kiss.
Rachel is a very lucky girl.
자, 그럼 출전자들을 입장시키죠
Let's get the contestants
out of their isolation booths.
입장했습니다!
And they're off!
내 오리 밟으면 어떻게 해!
심판!
Get your foot off my contestant!
Judge!
판결: 반칙 아님
Judge rules: No violation.
- 오리가 땅콩 쿠키를 먹어!
- 아냐! 저건 오래된 만두야
-The duck gets the Nutter Butter!
-No! That's just an old won ton.
판결: 땅콩 쿠키임!
Judge rules: Nutter Butter!
아리송했어
Tough call.
- 자연 다큐멘터리에 나왔어
- 잠깐만, 나도 그거 봤어!
-I saw it on the Discovery Channel.
-Wait a minute. I saw that!
맞아, 해파리에 관한 거였는데..
Yeah, about jellyfish,
and how if you..
네가 직접 오줌 쌌어?
You peed on yourself?
함부로 말하지 마!
알지도 못하면서 말야!
You can't say that! You don't know!
아파서 기절하는 줄 알았단 말야
I thought I'd pass out from the pain.
노력해 봤는데 그쪽으로
구부려지지가 않더라고
Anyway, I tried,
but I couldn't bend that way.
그래서
So..
그래, 내가 도와줬어!
That's right, I stepped up!
친구가 내 도움이 필요하대잖아!
She's my friend and she needed help!
필요하다면 너희한테도
오줌 눌 수 있어!
If I had to,
I'd pee on any one of you!
단짝 친구랄 건 없어요
Nope. No best friend.
그냥 다 같이 친합니다
Just a lot of close friends.
드라마 얘길 더 해보죠
So now back to the show.
엄청난 게이 팬들에 대해
어떻게 생각하세요?
How does it feel
to have a huge gay fan base?
정말요? 저한테요?
Really? Me?
전 엄청난 게이는 한명도 모르는데
Wow, I don't even know
any huge gay people.
내 가슴에 비수를 꽂네
It hurts me. It physically hurts me.
우리끼리 얘기지만
당신은 게이가 아니시죠?
Now, off the record, you're not..
왜? 내 남자 핸드백 때문에 그래?
What? Are you referring
to my man's bag?
처음엔 멋진 줄만 알았지
근데 실용적이기까지 해
At first, it just looked good,
but it's practical.
이것 봐, 구획이 다 정해져있다고
지갑에다 열쇠에다..
It's got compartments for stuff:
your wallet, your keys.
화장품까지
Your makeup.
얼굴과 얼굴이 마주보게 할까?
Should I climb down your front
so we're face to face..
아니면 엉덩이랑 얼굴이
마주보게 할까?
or should I climb down your back
so we're butt to face?
- 얼굴끼리가 낫겠지?
- 얼굴끼리로 해
-I think face is best.
-Yeah, face.
- 좋아, 내려간다
- 알았어
-Okay, here I come.
-All right.
맙소사, 도대체 체중이 몇이야?
Oh, my..
How much do you weigh, Ross?
지금은 대답 안할래
연휴 때 붙은 살이 안빠졌어
I prefer not to answer that. I'm still
carrying a little holiday weight.
아까 방향을 결정할 때
진지하게 생각 안한 것 같아
When we said "face to face," we didn't
think it all the way through!
- 피비
- 안녕
-Hey, Pheebs.
-Hey.
이것 봐
Check it out.
남성미가 쫙 흐르지?
How much of a man am I?
멋있다, 남성미뿐 아니라
창녀기도 다분해
Nice. Manly and also kind of a slut.
너 여자가 다됐구나
You're turning into a woman.
아냐! 왜 그런 말을 해?
정말 너무 못됐어!
No, I'm not! Why would you say that?
That's just mean!
나한테 화났어? 내가 뭐랬기에?
Now I've upset you? What did I say?
뭐랬다기보다 말투가 그렇잖아
Not what you said,
it's just the way you said it.
맙소사! 나 여잔가 봐!
Oh, my God! I'm a woman!
- 낮잠 잘 잤다
- 달콤했어
-Great nap.
-It really was.
저요? 게이요? 아녜요
Me? Gay? No. No. No.
하지만 친한 친구 중엔
게이가 많아요
But I have a number
of close friends who are.
이제 여자 얘길 해보죠
So let's talk about women.
여성 독자들이 당신의
연애 생활에 관심이 많거든요
I'm sure our female readers are
interested in your romantic life.
난 여자를 위아래로 보다
이렇게 얘길해
What I do is, I look a woman
up and down and I say:
'이봐, 안녕?'
"Hey. How you doing?"
됐어
Oh, please.
이봐, 안녕?
Hey. How you doing?
이 사람 차가 아주 멋진 포르쉐야
He has an amazing Porsche under there.
보여주고 싶지만 방금 잠들었어요
I'd love to show you, but I just
tucked her in. She's sleeping.
나랑 같이 한잔하러 안가겠어요?
Would you two girls
like to go for a drink?
- 레이첼 있어요? 난 동생인데
- 맙소사! 질!
-Is Rachel here? I'm her sister.
-Oh, my God! Jill!
- 맙소사! 레이첼!
- 어서 와!
-Oh, my God! Rachel!
-Oh, hi!
- 맙소사! 인사시켜줘!
- 여긴 챈들러고
-Oh, my God! Introduce us!
-Well, this is Chandler.
모니카랑 로스는 알지?
저긴 피비, 그리고 조이야
You know Monica and Ross.
That's Phoebe. That's Joey.
- 이봐, 안녕?
- 하지마!
-Hey, how you doing?
-Don't!
당신은 좋은 사람이고 친구로서
또 룸메이트로서 손색이 없지만
You're a really nice guy. I'm happy
to be your roommate and friend.
그냥 당신에 대해
그런 식으론 생각이 안돼요
I'm just.. You know, I just
don't feel that way about you.
어떻게 된 건지 알겠어
I see what happened.
내가 밀어내려고 해서 그런 거죠?
It's because I was trying
to repel you. Right?
내가 관심을 보여주면
지금과는 느낌이 확 다를걸요
Believe me, you'd feel
a lot different if I turned it on.
- 뭐 별로요
- 그렇다니까요
-I don't think so.
-Oh, I do.
이봐, 안녕?
How you doing?
안녕
I'm okay.
뭐? 맙소사!
What? Oh, dear God!
이렇다 할게 없어요
제가 수줍음이 많거든요
Not much to tell there.
I'm really shy.
다 됐습니다
인터뷰 끝마칠게요
So that's it.
I guess that's all I need.
정말 감사합니다
잡지는 내달 초에 나올 거예요
Thank you so much.
I think they'll run this next month.
좋아요, 감사합니다
Oh, great. Great. Thank you.
- 안녕히 계세요
- 안녕히 가세요
-Bye.
-Bye-bye.
- 성공이야
- 대단했어
-I did it.
-Amazing.
잠깐만요, 깜박했네요
이 질문은 늘 하는 건데
Wait, I almost forgot.
We have to ask everybody this:
우리 인생의 나날들 외에
어떤 드라마를 즐겨 보시죠?
Other than Days,
what's your favorite soap opera?
난 드라마 안 봐요
나도 생활이란 게 있다고요
Oh, I don't watch soap operas.
Excuse me? I have a life, you know?
감사합니다, 드라마 다이제스트
독자들이 기뻐하겠네요
The readers at Soap Opera Digest
will be happy to learn that.
별말씀을요
Good enough.
아슬아슬했어
So close.
드라마 안본다는 얘긴
기사에 안집어넣었네
They didn't put in the part
about you not watching soaps.
내가 전화해서 농담이었다고
했더니 빼주더라고
I called the lady and said l
was joking. She was nice about it.
- 그 여자랑 잤지?
- 조금
-You slept with her, didn't you?
-A little bit.
이 사진 정말 멋진데
This picture of you is steamy.
엄청난 게이 팬들을 위해
집어넣은 거야
That's just a little something
for my huge gay fan base.
- 방금 나한테 윙크했어?
- 그 사진 맘에 들어했잖아
-Did you just wink at me?
-You're the one who loves the picture.